Stanley Okonkwo

Web Developer

A goal driven and self-motivated graduate with over 3years of proven and tested programming experience, skilled in the art of translating design mockups and prototypes and writes modular back end code that is easily maintainable. Improved UX scores by 45% over company's previous best at Motionstudio

agrictime@gmail.com

Nnewi, Nigeria

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/stanleyokonkwo/

+2348079981193

https://potfoilo-master.vercel.app/

https://github.com/jaguar48

WORK EXPERIENCE

Backend Engineer

Motion-Studio

04/2021 - Present, Lagos, Nigeria Achievements/Tasks

- _ Currently working with a team to build tech products for clients.
- Written unit and integration tests that improved code quality.

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

CJGrandExchange

05/2021- 10/2021, Awka/Nigeria Achievements/Tasks

- Actively worked in an agile software development environment which utilized the Scrum process.
- Collaborated with in-house UI designer to create sleek and innovative design which improved user experience by 67%.
- Conceived and built optimized landing pages in HTML and CSS, including payment gateway integration and cross-browser compatibility which improved marketing by 50%.

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER ErrandBoy Ltd

04/2020 - 08/2020, Awka/Nigeria Achievements/Tasks

- Redesigned the data model according to the good patterns by removing the duplicate records from the database while increasing the query performance by up to 53%.
- Worked on a web application that utilized HTML, JavaScript, CSS3, React, Laravel and MySQL.
- Researched new technologies, software packages and hardware products for use in website projects.

EDUCATION

B.Sc. in Geological Science
NNAMDI AZIKIWE UNIVERSITY

11/2015 - 11/2019,

Awka, Nigeria

Courses

Hydrogeology

- Geophysical/Geological mapping of Afikpo Ebonyi state

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Multi Author blog app(03/2021 - 03/2021)

 A fun side project built with Bootstrap, Js, Python, Django. It accepts multi author with each having their unique dashboards where they can create contents, edit and delete. It also has a custom search feature.

Google search clone (02/2019 - 02/2019)

 A concept Google search engine that aims to emulate the feature of Google search engine, it enables users to search and view results on the same page just like google search engine. Google search was built on top React and Redux.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Cloud Developer Certification, Udacity (2021 - Present)

Certificate for completing cloud developer nano degree course.

LANGUAGES

English

lgb

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Football Coding Playing Games

Watching movies

Software Development

Web Development